Daniel Lam

A full-stack web developer with experience in animation, previzualization and VFX.

Over the years I've had to work with many different workflows and software packages, and understood how different companies tackle different problems and creating solutions or pipelines that suit their user's needs while following design principles to offer an engaging product.

Fresno, CA 93720 dann.lam@gmail.com (415) 509-1279

Experience

Web Developer

Bootcamp March 2023 - June 2023 Berkley, CA

- Lead projects with small teams creating minimum viable products.
- Create and manage databases using MongoDB and MySQL
- Create Express layer using Javascript for routing database
 CRUD actions
- Create UI/UX experiences using React/Javascript for user interactions.
- Setting up Node for server interactions
- App deployment to cloud platforms

Blockchain Asset Trader

Jan 2020 - Present

- Technical Analysis
- Risk Management
- Market Research

Layout Animator

The Third Floor Inc Los Angeles, CA June 2019 - December 2019

Layout Animator

Blur Studios Culver City, CA July 2017 - October 2018

- Character animation and motioncapture
- Character modelling and rigging
- Vehicle animation, rigging, texturing, and simulation
- Camera layout, blocking, and lighting
- Character rotoscoping and compositing

Education

UC Berkeley Bootcamp

University of California Berkeley, CA March 2023 - June 2023 Film Media BA

University of Rhode Island Kingston, RI September 2013 - June 2016